Guide to the Bob Fitch Photography Archive M1994
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: Southern Christian Leadership Conference/Coretta Scott King, 1965-1973, 2006-2014
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 591-595 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    SCLC 592 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 596-600 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    SCLC 596 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 601-605 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    SCLC 604 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 606-610 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 611-615 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 616-620 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 621-625 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 626-630 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 631-635 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    SCLC 631 removed to Fitch File [?].
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 636-640 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    SCLC 636 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 641-645 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 646-650 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 651-655 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    SCLC 654 and 655 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 656-660 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 661-665 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    SCLC 661 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 666-670 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 671-675 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 676-680 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 681-685 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 686-690 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    SCLC 686 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 691-695 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 696-700 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    SCLC 696 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 701-705 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 706-710 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 711-715 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    SCLC 712, 713 and 715 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 716-720 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 721-725 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    SCLC 721 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 726-730 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 731-735 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 736-740 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    SCLC 740 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 741-745 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 746-750 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    SCLC 748 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 751-755 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    SCLC 751 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 756-760 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    SCLC 756 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 761-765 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 776-780 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 781-785 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 786-790 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 791-795 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 796-800 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    SCLC 798 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 801-805 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 806-810 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 811-815 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 816-820 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 821-825 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    SCLC 825 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 826-830 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    SCLC 829 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 831-835 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    SCLC 835 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 836-840 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 841-845 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 846-850 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 851-855 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 856-860 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    SCLC 858 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 861-865 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 866-870 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 871-875 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 876-880 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 881-885 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 886-890 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 891-895 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 896-900 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 901-905 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 906-910 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 911-915 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 916-920 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 921-925 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 926-930 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 931-935 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    SCLC 932 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 936-940 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 941-945 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 946-950 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 951-955 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 956-960 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 961-965 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 966-970 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    SCLC 968 removed to Series 2: Classics.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 971-975 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    SCLC 971 missing or omitted.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: SCLC 976-979 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Vine City, Atlanta, Georgia [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Leroy Moton [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Randolph Blackwell 101-105 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Randolph Blackwell 106-110 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Duffel 101-107 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Buffett 101 [negatives], 1965-1973 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Oversized photos [prints], 1965-1966 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Prints are numbered 112, 120, 122, 125, 148, 224, 237, 246, 260, 266, 296, 297, 310, 354, 389, 442, 466, 487, 496, 530, 540, 543, 567, 592, 604, 628, 691, 724.
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Oversized photos [prints], 1966-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 822, 838, 932.
- Series 5: United Farm Workers/United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, 1969-1975, 1998-2014
  Contains mostly photographic materials: contact sheets, prints, negatives and slides. Additionally there is a small amount of correspondence, newspaper clippings, notes and audio materials. There are images related to this series in Series 2: Classics, Series 6: Black Star Agency, and Series 9: Computer Media/Digital Materials.
  This series documents the United Farm Workers, United Farm Workers Organizing Committee, Cesar Chavez and the farm workers' movement in California. Some of the individuals include: Dolores Huerta, Juanita Brown, Marion Moses, Jerry Cohen, Larry Itliong, Helen Chavez, Pete Valesco, Andy Imutan, Carlos Legrette, Manuel Uranday, Marshall Ganz, John Bank, Joan Baez, Taj Mahal, Andrew Young, Ron Dellums, Coretta Scott King, David Harris, and Daniel Ellsberg. The series records strikes, marches, picketing, demonstrations, funerals, and meetings. The series also documents Cesar Chavez's trip to the East Coast and Canada, where he spoke at several Congressional hearings and met with politicians, labor leaders, supporters, and boycott organizers.
  - United Farm Workers: Photo Identifications, 1969-2014 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - United Farm Workers: Correspondence and notes, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Includes correspondence from Cesar Chavez, Mark Day and Howard Chapnick.
  - United Farm Workers: Wayne State University correspondence, 2011 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - United Farm Workers: Correspondence and clippings [part 1 of 2], 1970, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - United Farm Workers: Correspondence and clippings [part 2 of 2], 1970, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - United Farm Workers: Transcript of interview with Cesar Chavez, 1969-1975 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Baltimore, Maryland [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 169-207.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Baltimore, Maryland [prints], 1969 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    Prints are numbered 140, 182, 262, 378, 425.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Washington D.C. [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 126-130, 132-168, 170, 282.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Washington D.C. [prints], 1969 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    Prints are numbered 126, 128, 132, 134, 135, 140, 142, 143, 149, 151, 152, 154, 159, 167, 334.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Atlantic City, New Jersey [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 208, 209, 211-220.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    Contact sheets are numbered 221-226, 228-236, 238-242, 475.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania [prints], 1969 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    Prints are numbered 222, 233, 235, 238, 242.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - New York City, New York [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 245-256, 258-265, 267-279, 281, 283-296, 317.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - New York City, New York [prints], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Prints are numbered 243, 245, 247, 253, 254, 255, 262, 264, 268, 272, 273, 294, 295, 317, 398.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Boston, Massachusetts [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered 131, 297-316, 318.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Boston, Massachusetts [prints], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Prints are numbered 300, 310, 312, 316.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Montreal, Canada [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 319-337.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Montreal, Canada [prints], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    Prints are numbered 323, 340, 348.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Toronto, Canada [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 341, 344, 346-361.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Toronto, Canada [prints], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    Prints are numbered 253, 321, 346, 350, 353-356, 360.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Ottawa, Canada [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 338-340, 342, 343, 345.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Ottawa, Canada [prints], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    Prints are numbered 321, 338, 342, 356, 383.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Buffalo, New York [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 237, 362-364.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Buffalo, New York [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    Contact sheets are numbered 227, 365, 367-378, 380-387.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Buffalo, New York [prints], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    Prints are numbered 227, 365, 367-378, 380-387.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Cleveland, Ohio [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 379, 388-393.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Cleveland, Ohio [prints], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Prints are numbered 317, 388, 389, 392.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Detroit, Michigan [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    Contact sheets are numbered 394-409, 417-419.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Detroit, Michigan [prints], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    Prints are numbered 284, 287, 365, 373, 377, 378, 382, 387, 396, 398, 399, 403-409, 420.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Chicago, Illinois [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    Contact sheets are numbered 410, 421-440, 442-446.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour - Chicago, Illinois [prints], 1969 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Prints are numbered 265, 388, 390, 391, 409, 423, 425, 429, 430, 433, 435-437, 442.
  - United Farm Workers: East Coast-Canada Tour [slides], 1969 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - United Farm Workers: Images for Stanford Web [slides], 1969-1975 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - United Farm Workers: Images for Stanford Web [slides], 1969-1975 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - United Farm Workers: Miscellaneous [negatives], 1969-1975 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - United Farm Workers: 647 Delano and Salinas, California [contact sheets], 1969-1971 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1375-1378, 1380-1400, 1402-1407, 1503, 1505, 1506, 1508, 1509, 1512-1516, 1520-1522, 1524, 1525, 1529, 1531, 1532, 1545, 1546, 1763, 1764, 2060, 2314, 2315, 2427-2438.
  - United Farm Workers: 647 Delano and Salinas, California [prints], 1969-1973 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    Prints are numbered 591, 1381, 1386, 1394, 1401, 1402, 1503, 1511, 1512, 1514, 1516, 1531, 2022, 2029, 2030, 2071, 2427, 2432, 2435, 3813.
  - United Farm Workers: 647 Delano, Salinas and Coachella [slides], 1970 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - United Farm Workers: 647 Delano, Salinas and other locations [contact sheets and notes], 1973-1974 (Box 68)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3767, 3795, 3977, 2105, 2151, 2152, 2155-2165, 3924, 3928, 3951-3953, 3955, 3958, 3960, 4260, 4266.
  - United Farm Workers: 648 Salinas Lettuce Strike, Salinas, California [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2015-2020, 2022-2035, 2045-2059, 2061-2072, 2098-2104, 2372, 2419.
  - United Farm Workers: 648 Salinas Lettuce Strike, Salinas, California [prints], 1970-1973 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Prints are numbered 1503, 2016, 2026-2029, 2032, 2053, 2056, 2064, 2070, 2072, 2102, 2103, 2412, 2415, 2417, 2421, 3975.
  - United Farm Workers: 648 Salinas Lettuce Strike, Salinas, California [slides], 1970 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - United Farm Workers: 649 UFW/Teamsters fight, Coachella, California [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3756-3770, 3790-3794, 3796-3853.
  - United Farm Workers: 649 UFW/Teamsters fight, Coachella, California [prints], 1973 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Prints are numbered 3756, 3759, 3762-3764, 3767-3770,3792, 3794, 3800-3802, 3804, 3805, 3810, 3812, 3813, 3816, 3818, 3822, 3824, 3825, 3832, 3834, 3839, 3840, 3842.
  - United Farm Workers: 649 UFW/Teamsters fight, Coachella, California [slides], 1973 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - United Farm Workers: 650 Nagi Daifallah funeral, Delano, California [contact sheets], August 17, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3950-3960.
  - United Farm Workers: 650 Nagi Daifallah funeral, Delano, California [prints], August 17, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    Prints are numbered 3951, 3952, 3954-3958.
  - United Farm Workers: 650 Nagi Daifallah funeral, Delano, California [slides], August 17, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - United Farm Workers: 651 Giumarra Ranch arrests, near Bakersfield, California [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3973, 3974, 3976, 3978, 3979.
  - United Farm Workers: 651 Giumarra Ranch arrests, near Bakersfield, California [slides and prints], 1973 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - United Farm Workers: 652 Picket, Lamont, California [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3861-3871, 3893-3908, 3975, 3980-3984.
  - United Farm Workers: 652 Picket, Lamont, California [prints], 1973 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Prints are numbered 3862, 3864, 3869, 3871, 3895, 3901, 3903, 3904, 3981, 3983.
  - United Farm Workers: 652 Picket, Lamont, California [slides], 1973 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - United Farm Workers: 653 Juan de la Cruz funeral, Delano, California [contact sheets and notes], August 21, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Juan de la Cruz funeral and procession, Delano, California. Includes Dolores Huerta, Cesar Chavez, Joan Baez, Taj Mahal and Marshall Ganz.
    Contact sheets are numbered 3961-3972.
  - United Farm Workers: 653 Juan de la Cruz funeral, Delano, California [slides], August 21, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - United Farm Workers: 654 Organizing meeting, Fresno, California [slides], 1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - United Farm Workers: 655 Constitutional Convention, Fresno, California [contact sheets], September, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4070, 4079-4088, 4090.
  - United Farm Workers: 655 Constitutional Convention, Fresno, California [prints], September, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Prints are numbered 4083, 4090.
  - United Farm Workers: 655 Constitutional Convention, Fresno, California [slides], September, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - United Farm Workers: 656 National Farm Workers Safeway pickets [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4104.
  - United Farm Workers: 657 National Farm Workers-Gallo March, Modesto, California [contact sheets], 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4285, 4287, 4369-4388.
  - United Farm Workers: 657 National Farm Workers-Gallo March, Modesto, California [prints], 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    Prints are numbered 4262, 4263, 4371-4378, 4381, 4384, 4388.
  - United Farm Workers: 657 National Farm Workers-Gallo March, Modesto, California [slides], March 1, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - United Farm Workers: 657 National Farm Workers-Gallo March, Modesto, California [slides], March 1, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - United Farm Workers: 658 Paulo Agbayani Retirement Village, Delano, California [contact sheets], June 15, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4261-4266.
  - United Farm Workers: 658 Paulo Agbayani Retirement Village, Delano, California [slides and prints], June 15, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - United Farm Workers: 659 Saludado family [contact sheets and notes], 1971, 2012 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered rolls 1837-1843, 1845-1861, 1881-1891, 1893, 1894, 1896, 1897, 2008-2014.
    Soy Chicano: I am Mexican-American, the book created using notes and images found in this file, has been digitized and can be viewed through this link:
    https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/10457931
  - United Farm Workers: 660 Cesar Chavez [contact sheets], 1969-1975 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1451-1454.
  - United Farm Workers: 661 Health clinics [contact sheets], 1969-1975 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3429-3436, 3438, 3439.
  - United Farm Workers: 661 Health clinics [prints], 1969-1975 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Prints are numbered 3430, 3433, 3437.
  - United Farm Workers: 662 Meetings at La Paz Headquarters [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1892, 1894, 1895.
  - United Farm Workers: 662 Meetings at La Paz Headquarters [prints], 1970 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Prints are numbered 1892, 1894, 1895.
  - United Farm Workers: 663 Olivos wedding, Kern County, California [contact sheets], 1969-1975 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1501, 1504, 1507, 1517-1519, 1523, 1526-1528, 1530, 1537, 1543, 1544, 1555.
  - United Farm Workers: 664 First growers contract, Coachella, California [contact sheets], May, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1806-1817.
  - United Farm Workers: 664 First growers contract, Coachella, California [prints and slides], May, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - United Farm Workers: 665 Joan Baez concert and Salinas organizing campaign [contact sheets], 1969-1975 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    Andrew Young, Dolores Huerta, Coretta Scott King, Ron Dellums and Marshall Ganz in Salinas during strike and organizing campaign while Cesar Chavez was in jail. Also includes images of Joan Baez and David Harris at a UFW rally in San Jose, California.
    Contact sheets are numbered 2412-2418, 2420-2422, 2877, 2882, 2883, 2886, 2887.
  - United Farm Workers: 665 Joan Baez concert and Salinas organizing campaign [prints], 1969-1975 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    Prints are numbered 2412, 2419, 2886.
  - United Farm Workers: 666 Organizing [contact sheets], 1971-1973 (Box 71, Folder 14)